homenetpro.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy - HomeNetPro.com

## Last Updated: 7-24-14

HomeNetPro.Com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. Period."

### How we gather information from users

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our site. 

Like most Web sites, HomeNetPro.Com also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. 

As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences.

### What we do with the information we collect

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on HomeNetPro.Com to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by HomeNetPro.Com and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by HomeNetPro.Com may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. 

We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. 

We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

### Affiliated sites, Linked sites and Advertisements

HomeNetPro.Com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a HomeNetPro.Com page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. 

Also, through HomeNetPro.Com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. HomeNetPro.Com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. 

Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. HomeNetPro.Com does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of HomeNetPro.Com and this policy.

### Children/Minors

HomeNetPro.Com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe HomeNetPro.Com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed below.

### Contacting Us

### We Can be Reached by Contacting

**Email:** support (at) homenetpro (dot) com

**Snail Mail:** Southwest Web Technologies, LLC 703 Hickory St. Carlsbad, NM 88220.

### Changes to this Policy

HomeNetPro.Com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

### Governing law

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by US law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Carlsbad, NM. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following location: Carlsbad, NM. under the rules of the US Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.

HomeNetPro.Com is controlled, operated and administered entirely within HomeNetPro.Com. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

## Privacy Policy Continued...

**This is the web site of:** Southwest Web Technologies, LLC

**Our postal address is:   **703 Hickory St.  
                                    Carlsbad, NM 88220

We can be reached via e-mail at: Support (at) HomeNetPro (dot) com

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address except for the IP address of the originating visitor..

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending email to us at the above address and telling us that you do not want to receive e-mail from our company.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending email to us at the above address or writing to us at the above address.

### Our Commitment to Privacy

Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine quality products and services with integrity in dealing with our users. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.

### What Information Do We Collect?

When you visit our site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you actively choose to disclose ("Active Information") and use information collected, in a way not visible to you, on an aggregate anonymous basis as you and others browse our site ("Passive Information").

If you choose to post information on our site or maintain email, snailmail or telephone contact with us, we may retain such information also.

### No Use of Our Site by Persons Under 13

No person under 13 should disclose information on this site. You may learn more about protecting children's privacy online by visiting www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy. ****

### Passive Information Collected

Our site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" to collect information about how our site is used. Passive Information gathered may include the date and time of visits, the site pages viewed, time spent at our site, the sites visited just before and just after our site. Passive Information is collected on an aggregate basis without any association to your personal information so that you remain anonymous. If you do not wish to transmit "cookie" information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser; please consult the "Help" section of your browser to correctly do so.

### What is a Cookie?

Cookies are a feature of web browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Chrome, Netscape Navigator, etc.) software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a site. They are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's web browser on one site to simplify subsequent interactions with that site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transaction on related web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from site to site and to complete transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized. To find out more about cookies, including how to disable and/or remove cookies, please visit www.cookiecentral.com

### Do-Not-Track

The Site does not currently respond to browser “do not track” signals or other similar mechanisms.

### How Do We Use the Information Collected?

Broadly speaking, persons we employ directly, or as contractors or agents at our direction, use Active Information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer services such as support, and making available other products or services we think may be of interest to our users. We may use the Active Information or Passive Information you provide to us to contact you about changes to our site, new services, features or products we offer, or other information we think you shall find valuable. If at any time you do not wish to receive such information, please send us an email .

We use Passive Information to gather information about our users and to enhance and design our site to make it easier, faster and friendlier to use. Additionally, cookies help us know information about how many people visit our site, when they visit and how they use our service. We do not connect any of this information to your personal information or email address. However, Passive Information may result in your viewing of particular advertising based on your user habits for your viewing on our site.

### Your Information In Relation to Others We Link To

You may be able to access other websites through our site. When you do so you are doing so subject to their policies regarding privacy and data collection and you should read those sites' privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such sites. When you choose to shop at such sites, you should read their privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before making purchases.

### Sharing Information with Advertisers or Other Third Parties

We may disclose anonymous information about user habits, characteristics and user patterns, based on aggregate user statistics to advertisers on our site.

### Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law

We may be required by law or government agency to disclose both Active and Passive Information you have provided to us. If you were referred by an affiliate partner of ours, your name and email address may be shared with them when you place an order at our site.

### How Do We Secure Active Information and Passive Information?

We secure your personal information submitted by you by using reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of Active Information and Passive Information. Your postings on this site and other communications you may have with us via email or snail mail may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your sending information. Therefore, if you choose to communicate with us through these means, you are assuming the risk of doing so and we request that you do not send or post sensitive information through these means.

### How Can You Choose Not to Receive Information About Products or Services By Us or to Correct, Delete or Access Your Information

If you desire not to receive information about products or services we think may be of interest to you or if you wish to access, delete or correct you information, please send us an email to support (at) homenetpro.com

We reserve the right to revise this policy at our discretion. Please check back on this site as this policy may be revised from time to time without notice to you.
